adonit.net 2019-06-18

# Privacy Policy

### **Adonit Creative Inc.**

#### **Privacy Policy**

##### **(Revised June 2018)**

Adonit Creative Inc. **(“Adonit,” “our,” “us,” or "we")** respects your privacy. We created this Privacy Policy to let you know what information we collect and how we use it, as well as our information sharing and protection practices.

This Privacy Policy applies to:

  * The website www.adonit.net (the **“Website”** );
  * The Forge mobile application (the **“App”** );
  * Information collected by Adonit from third party applications ( **“Non-Adonit Apps”** ) that integrate our Adonit software development kit ( **“SDK”** ); and
  * Any email, text and other electronic communications you send to Adonit through the Website or the App.

This Privacy Policy does _not_ apply to:

  * Information we collect offline or by any other means (such as through other websites, products or services we may offer);
  * Information collected by any third parties, including through Non-Adonit Apps, which may have their own privacy policies.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully and save it. If you do not agree with it, you should not access the Website or download the App or Non-Adonit Apps that interface with our SDK. By using the Website, the App or Non-Adonit Apps, you consent to the practices prescribed in this Privacy Policy.

**What information does Adonit collect?**

  * **Personal Information.** When we refer to **"Personal Information"** in this Privacy Policy, we mean any information by which you may be personally identified or contacted, whether online or offline. When you purchase products on the Website or otherwise fill out any forms located on the Website, we may collect certain Personal Information from you, such as your first and last name, email address, phone number, mailing address or other contact information and credit card or other payment information. When you download the App, we collect your email address. It is always your choice whether or not to provide Personal Information. If you choose not to provide requested Personal Information, you may not be able to participate in certain activities or use certain features of the Website.
  * **Technical Information.** We may also collect and use technical data and related information, such as information about your device, system and application software, peripherals and other data related to your interactions with the Website, the App and our SDK ( **“Technical Information”** ). We may automatically collect Technical Information through cookies and log files. The information we collect from these technologies includes your stylus serial number, stylus model and version, stylus user settings, application used, iPad model, iOS version, Adonit SDK version, stylus connection and disconnection times, usage data, crash analytics, IP address, browser type, referring page and time of visit. Adonit does not consider this information to be Personal Information, but note that the IP address and stylus serial number may potentially be used in a personally identifying manner.

**Information You Voluntarily Disclose**

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose Information through any public-facing features of the Website, the App or Non-Adonit Apps that interface with our SDK (for example, via message boards), that information can be collected and used by others. You submit this information at your own risk. We are not responsible for the security or privacy of any information you choose to submit in connection with these public features.

**How does Adonit use Information?**

Except as described in this Privacy Policy or in our Terms of Use or similar document, Personal Information and Technical Information (collectively, **“Information”** ) that you provide or that we collect will be kept confidential and used to support your relationship with Adonit.

We may use your Information, including your Personal Information, as follows:

  * To improve, market or promote Adonit’s products (including our stylus products) and services.
  * To increase our understanding of how users prefer to use our stylus products
  * To improve the SDK and application integration of the SDK
  * To enhance the user experience, display personalized content or enable you to participate in features of the Website or the App.
  * To communicate with you, including about the Website, the App or the SDK.
  * To alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new products and services offered by Adonit or its third party partners.
  * To respond to comments, questions or requests for customer service.
  * To display advertisements, including advertisements from third parties.
  * For any other purpose we may describe when you provide the Information.

We may also use your Information for any other purpose with your consent.

**Information We Share**

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, Adonit does not share, rent or sell your Personal Information collected through the Website, the App or the SDK with third parties.

Adonit or its agents, vendors or contractors may disclose Information, including your Personal Information, to third parties in the following circumstances:

  * To our agents, vendors or contractors that we use to support the internal operations of our business (including Shopify, our ecommerce partner) who are required to keep the Information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
  * If required to do so by law, comply with legal process or to comply with a governmental or regulatory request; 
  * To protect and defend the rights or property of Adonit or its agents or contractors; 
  * To enforce our Terms of Use or other Adonit agreements;
  * To act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Website or the public; and 
  * As part of a transaction or potential transaction where Adonit merges with another organization, files for bankruptcy, or sells its assets or capital stock.

**Security of Your Information**

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards designed to protect the Information. These safeguards include only storing Technical Information on our servers. Despite the actions and precautions we take, no data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of the Information and you acknowledge and agree that you transmit it to us at your own risk.

**Third-Party Websites, Services and Technologies**

We may provide links to Non-Adonit Apps and third party websites on the Website or in other communications to you. These links may appear as a specific domain name or URL or may be activated by clicking on an advertisement or other icon or graphic. Please be aware that other websites and services, including Non-Adonit Apps that integrate with our SDK, may collect personally identifiable information about you. We cannot control and are not responsible for the information collection practices of any Non-Adonit Apps or other third party websites or services. We encourage you to carefully review their terms of use, privacy policies, and any other legal notifications before using or providing information through such Non-Adonit Apps, websites, or services.

Further, the Website or the App may employ third party technologies that require you to accept such third party’s terms. This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of those third-party technologies.

**International Transfers**

Information collected from you may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Adonit or its affiliates, subsidiaries, agents or contractors maintain facilities. If you are accessing the Website from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use, please note that you are agreeing to the transfer of your data to the United States and processing globally. By providing your Information, you consent to any transfer and processing in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**Children’s Privacy**

The Website, the App and the SDK are not intended for children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect Information from children under 13. If you believe that we may have collected Information from a child under the age of 13, please contact us at support@adonit.net.

**Information Choices and Changes**

We may need to communicate with you about the Website, the App or the SDK, and we would like to make certain commercial offers available to you from time to time. As such, by signing up for our newsletter or by providing your email address through the use of our App, you consent to receive commercial messages (whether by phone, email, text or push notifications) from us or our third party partners, and acknowledge and agree that your primary phone numbers and email addresses and other information may be used for the purpose of initiating commercial messages. We will allow you to opt-out of receiving commercial messages. If you have subscribed to one of our services, you may unsubscribe by following the instructions that are included in e-mail that you receive. 

Cookies are small digital signature files that are stored by your web browser that allow your preferences to be recorded when visiting the website. Also they may be used to track your return visits to the Website. Depending on your browser, you may be able to remove and reject cookies from our Website by changing your browser settings. The default setting of many browsers is set to accept cookies until you change your settings. Please note that if you disable or refuse cookies, certain features of the Website may become inaccessible or may not function properly.

**Information Choices and Changes**

This is our entire Privacy Policy and it replaces any earlier version. We may change this Privacy Policy by posting a new version on the Website or distributing a new version via the App, and it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy periodically. If we make material changes to our practices regarding the collection, use and sharing of your Personal Information, we will notify you via e-mail to the email address you provide to us and/or through a notice in the App or on the Website home page.

When we do change the Privacy Policy, we will also revise the “revised” date. Your continued use of the Website, the App or the SDK after such date constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates. 

****Shipping Policy****

Because we ship from multiple warehouses, outside the US, CA, EU, ETA is 9 -15 working days for any items that may ship from international warehouses.If you are shipping an item outside the US, CA, you should consider using a trackable shipping service. EU or worldwide, please choose Royal Mail Tracked(Tracking Number Available).

****Lithium Batteries for International Shipment****

The carrier will restrict lithium Batteries for international shipping; It may take longer to delivery or cancel.

**Contacting Adonit**

For questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at Adonit Creative Inc., 1524 S I-35, Suite 302, Austin, TX 78704, and support@adonit.net.
